>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们一直在谈论这个单位的词法范围，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We've been talking
about lexical scope in this unit, and
这是一个基本的理解让它能够进入封闭状态
that is a foundational understanding
to be able to jump into closure.
你们当中有多少人曾经听过或接受过这个采访的问题，
How many of you have ever heard or
given that interview question before,
什么是封闭的然后答案好像有点模糊
what is closure and then the answer
seems to sort of fumble around like,
有关异步回调的信息吗 ?
something about asynchronous callbacks?
我认为封闭是最主要的，它肯定是最常见的
I think closure is one of the most, it's
certainly one of the most prevalent and
也许是计算机科学发明的最重要的想法之一
maybe one of the most important ideas
ever invented in computer science.
平心而论，我在这过程中提到过几次我有一些
In all fairness, I've mentioned a few
times in this course that I have some
和道格的意见分岐但是他道格 - 克劳福有很多
disagreements with Doug, but he,
Doug Crawford, has had a lot of
他为我们的产业做了很多事情，做了很多他说的事情。
really great things that he's done for our
industry and a lot of things that he said.
当他说一些聪明的东西时，他应该得到它的功劳。
And when he says something brilliant,
he deserves credit for it.
多年前他有个演讲说他在讲计算机科学
Years ago, he had a conference talk that
he was giving about computer science
在计算机科学历史的过程中创造的东西
things that have been created over the
course of the history of computer science.
他想说的是，本质上，所有伟大的想法都需要一个整体
And he was making a point that,
essentially, all great ideas take a whole
在他们开始实施之前，先生成程序员，然后再开始流行。
generation of programmers before they get
implemented, before they become popular.
他给出了各种各样的例子。
And he gave a variety of examples.
当他去解释为什么这种现象存在的时候
And when he went to explain
why that phenomenon exists,
是一种以脸颊为反应的舌头
it was sort of a tongue in
cheek kind of response or
解释，这有点半真半假。
explanation, which is kind
of half-true and half-funny.
他说，好吧，之所以花一代人的时间，是因为我们如此
He said, well, the reason why it takes
a full generation is because we're so
固执的
stubborn.
我们被困住了
We're stuck in our ways.
所以我们得等现在这一代人都死了
So we have to wait around for
all of the current generation to die or
在新的伟大构想开始之前就退休了
retire llll before the new
great idea picks up.
再一次，这就像是半真半乐。
[LAUGH] Again,
it's like half-true and half-funny.
但他继续说我们知道关闭一定很棒
But he went on to say we know that closure
must be truly great cuz it took two
让我们的世代都能抓住
full generations to catch on.
我们真的要等很多人死或退休了
[LAUGH] We really had to wait for
a lot of people to die or retire.
它是所有编程中最普遍的概念之一。
It's one of the most prevalent
concepts in all of programming.
然而当它在 90 年代中期引入 JavaScript 的时候
And yet, when it was introduced in
JavaScript in the mid to late 90s,
在某种程度上是一种革命性的想法
it was somewhat of a revolutionary
idea that we would take
一种表面上为普通男人设计的语言
a language that was ostensibly
designed for the common man,
以消费为导向的开发者，而不是学术机构。
the consumer-oriented developer,
not the academic.
专为他们设计，旨在构建面向客户的应用程序和
Designed for them, designed to build
consumer-oriented applications and
消费驱动的应用。
consumer-driven applications.
通常情况下，这些语言没有在功能部件上进行选择。
Those sorts of languages didn't
pick up on features, typically,
都是用学术语言来的
that had only really been
in academic languages.
所以封闭并不是新的，它是从一开始就开始的，非常早的几天。
So closure was not new, that was around
from the very beginning, very early days.
在 Lisp 和其他类似的地方
In Lisp and other things like that.
但是它有点分裂
But it was somewhat of a divide,
那里有被认为是没有真正的开发者的地方
where there were features that were
considered to be, no real developer,
没有一个非学术的开发者会用类似的封闭物
no non-academic developer will ever
use something like closure, okay?
然后在 1995年布伦丹 - 艾希被雇去网景时
And then in 1995, when Brendan Eich was
hired to go to Netscape, the story goes
他表面上是去了，他想把方案放在浏览器里。
that ostensibly he was going there and he
was wanting to put scheme in the browser.
计划是一种旧的功能性编程语言。
Scheme being an old functional
programming language.
这不一定是学术语言，
It is not necessarily
an academic language, but
我认为可以说是一九九五年的一种学术语言。
I think it can arguably be
an academic language in 1995.
所以他想把它放在浏览器里。
And so
he wanted to put that in the browser.
Netscape 的人说，不，不，那永远不起作用。
And the Netscape folks said,
no, no, no, that'll never work.
没人会写那种语言
Nobody will ever write that language.
您需要使用类似于 Java的语言。
You need to make a language
that looks like Java.
现在我不在那儿
Now, I wasn't there,
但我想知道布兰登对他的态度有点不灵
but I like to imagine in my mind that
Brendan is sort of sauntering back to his
令人失望的是，愚蠢的 Netscape 不会让我在浏览器上实施计划。
disappointed, like, stupid Netscape
won't let me put scheme on the browser.
然后他就有了那个灯泡的想法他说我知道我会怎么做
And then he has that light bulb idea and
he says, I know what I'll do,
我会把计划放在浏览器里，但我会称之为 " JavaScript" 。
I'll put scheme in the browser but
I'll call it JavaScript.
我让它看起来像 Java 我把它叫做 " JavaScript"
I'll make it look like Java and
I'll call it JavaScript.
这就是它的本质。
And that's essentially what it is.
这种 JavaScript 很可能在某些方面
That JavaScript is probably,
in some respects,
与类似计划有关，甚至与 Java 或 C++ 相关。
related to something like Scheme,
than even to Java or C++.
是啊我们用花括号和分号
Yeah, we use curly braces and semicolons.
这很困难
And it's real hard.
来自功能编程语言的一些核心概念是
Some of those core concepts from
functional programming languages were
或者至少计划从那一天起就开始了
there, or at least planned,
from really the day one of the language.
我认为这是 JavaScript 成功的原因之一
And I think that's one of the reasons
why JavaScript succeeded and
幸免于会，成为当今普遍存在的语言。
survived, and thrived and became
the ubiquitous language that it is today.
事实上我想说的是
Matter of fact,
I like to suggest, essentially,
他是个意外的天才
that this was kind of
accidental genius on his part.
不要以任何方式贬低他，但我不认为有任何可能的方法
Not to disparage him in any way, but
I don't think there's any possible way any
人类可以想象到 1995 年
human being could have imagined
in 1995 that this little
原型语言 [LAUGH] 最终会被普遍存在。
prototype language [LAUGH] would end
up being as ubiquitous is today.
电视，冰箱，手表，眼镜，还有
That it is in TVs and refrigerators,
and watches, and glasses, and
灯泡和电脑还有智能手机
light bulbs, and computers,
and smartphones.
全球数十亿美元的设备。
Billions and
billions of devices worldwide.
机器人我是说我不认为你能想象
Robots, I mean, I don't think you
could have possibly imagined that
这种语言将会成为一个普遍的用例。
the language would have served
such a widespread use case.
我想证明这一点的原因是语言能得到认可
And I think a testament to it is because
the language embraced an approachable
语法，或至少当时认为是可核准的语法。
syntax, or at least what was felt to
be an approachable syntax at the time.
但给它带来了一些前所未有的最强大的特征。
But brought it some of the most powerful
features that had ever been invented.
在这种情况下，关闭。
In that case, closure.
在那个地方，它真的是第一个重要的搬家公司。
And it was really kind of one of
the first major movers in that space.
我是说你可以说唯一的其他语言
I mean, arguably,
you could say that the only other language
在当时真的开始变得更加消费导向型的时候
at the time that was really maybe starting
to become more consumer-oriented and
那就是明珠
had closure would have been Pearl.
所以 JavaScript要么是第一个要么是
So JavaScript's either the first or
几乎是朝那个方向移动的第一语言
nearly the first language
to move in that direction.
而在 24 年后的今天，每一种语言都有
And as things stand today,
24 years later, every single language has
因为事实证明关闭才是最重要的
closure because it turns out that
closure is just that important.
那么在这个基础上，
And so with that foundation, then,
让我觉得很麻烦的事情
it strikes me as troublesome
that something that is so
伟大而又无处不在的事物是我们仍然会跌跌跌去的
great and so pervasive is something
that we still stumble over.
我们甚至不能给出一个定义。
And we can't even give a definition of.
我们甚至无法给出精确的例子。
We can't even really
give precise examples of.
事实上我想说的是你们每个人都是 JavaScript 开发人员
In fact, I'd go so far as to say every one
of you that is a JavaScript developer,
如果你写了 JavaScript
if you've written JavaScript for
超过三个小时，您已通过某种方式，形状或表单与关闭进行交互。
more than three hours, you have interacted
with closure in some way, shape, or form.
事实上大多数人都是整天都在做
And in fact,
most of you do it all the time, all day,
每天都没有实现，在各种不同的范例中。
every day without even realizing it,
in various different paradigms.
它不仅是使用闭包的功能编程
It's not only functional
programming that uses closure, but
在许多不同的地方使用了封闭物。
closure is used in lots
of different places.
它用于异步 AJAX。
It's used for asynchronous AJAX.
它用于各种不同的事物。
It's use for
all sorts of different things.
因此，我希望我们花一点时间来更确切地说明这一点。
And so I want us to take a moment
to be more precise about it.
现在，作为一个想法的结束实际上是在预测计算机科学，
Now, closure as an idea is actually
predating computer science,
它实际上是从 lambda 演算出来的
it actually comes to us
from lambda calculus.
这个封闭的想法
This idea of closure,
它甚至在这个意义上预先设想了一种编程语言的概念。
it even predates the idea of
a programming language in that sense.
如果我想给你看一堆符号
And so if I were to try to show
you a bunch of symbols and
教你 lambda 演算我完全不知道这个任务
teach you lambda calculus,
I am completely not up to that task.
我读过 Wikipedia 的 lambda 演算。
I have read the Wikipedia page for
lambda calculus.
我知道这是件事
I know it is a thing.
我什么都不知道
I don't know anything about it.
我一点都不明白
I don't understand it at all.
我有个 CS 背景但我还是不明白
And I have a CS background and
I still don't get it.
所以至少从我的角度来看
So it turns out that,
at least from my perspective,
学术定义，关闭的数学定义，不有用。
the academic definition, the mathematical
definition for closure, not useful.
事实上，就算你去维基百科
Matter of fact,
even if you go to Wikipedia and
你想问问维基百科什么是封闭的
you try to ask Wikipedia what is closure,
or
如果你去找一本电脑科学教科书问它，什么是封闭的 ?
if you try to go to a computer science
textbook and ask it, what is closure?
我的意思是，我在学校教过这些东西，但没有任何东西卡住了。
I mean, I was taught those things in
school, but none of that ever stuck.
从没有过任何点击
None of it ever clicked.
所以我要用另一个定义代替
So I'm gonna try to substitute a different
definition, which instead of focusing on
学者们关注我们在我们的节目中能观察到的
the academics, focuses on what we can
observe in our programs that is different
因为关闭是语言的特征。
as a result of closure being
a characteristic of the language.
要了解此定义，您必须了解词法作用域。
To understand this definition,
you have to understand lexical scope.
这就是我们在这方面建立自己的原因。
That's why we've built
ourselves in this direction.
我们正朝模块模式前进
We're headed towards the module pattern,
沿着这条路走的路是我们必须明白的
and a step along the way is
we've gotta understand closure.
如果你不理解词法范围就不能去了
Can't get there if you don't
understand lexical scope.